ffffound.com 2008-05-11

# FFFFOUND!

### Privacy Policy

Respecting users' privacy is important to FFFFOUND!. Read this page to learn about personal information that FFFFOUND! collects and how it may be used.

#### FFFFOUND! Database

The e-mail address you register with FFFFOUND! and the logs of your image-posting activity is used to calculate personalized recommendations as part of our service. We use this information in aggregate to generate statistics and other usage information. We share this information with you, other end users, and other third parties. 

#### Links to Third Party Web Sites

Our service may contain links to other websites and software. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these websites or software. Please visit the privacy policies of these third party sites in order to understand their privacy and information collection practices. 

#### Disclosures Required by Law

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information when we believe in good faith that an applicable law, regulation, or legal process requires it, or when we believe disclosure is necessary to protect or enforce our rights or the rights of another user. 

#### Cookies

Cookies are small text files stored by your browser on your computer when you visit a website. We use cookies to improve our website and make it easier to use. Cookies permit us to recognize you and avoid repetitive requests for the same information. Most browsers will accept cookies until you change your browser settings to refuse them. You may change your browser's settings to refuse our cookies. 

|  | 

### 個人情報の取り扱い

#### 個人情報の保護方針

個人情報の取扱いに関する法令、国が定める指針その他の規範を守ります。

#### 利用目的

メールアドレス、利用者の画像の嗜好情報は、利用者へのおすすめ画像の選別に利用されます。  
収集した利用者情報は、統計、解析され、利用者や第三者に開示されることがあります。  
ただしこの統計情報に、本人を特定できる情報はこの中には一切含みません。

#### 第三者への提供について

運営者は、取得した個人情報を、以下のいずれかに該当する場合を除いて、第三者には提供または開示しません。

  * 本人の同意がある場合
  * 生命、身体または財産の保護のために必要な場合で、本人の同意をいただくことが困難な場合 
  * その他法令に基づいて開示・提供を求められた場合

#### クッキーに関して

クッキー（Cookies）とは、ウェブサイトが利用者を識別するための手段として、お客様のコンピューターに送付し記録されるデータの一つです。  
本サービスでは、提供する情報やサービスを充実させたり、より便利に利用していただくために、クッキーを使用�
